<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-01-09T00:52:45-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Novels by Tom</title><subtitle>Just novels I&apos;m writing to increase my english level</subtitle><entry><title type="html">A slacker</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/nonsense/2025/01/04/leon-the-slacker.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A slacker" /><published>2025-01-04T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-04T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/nonsense/2025/01/04/leon-the-slacker</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/nonsense/2025/01/04/leon-the-slacker.html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>VIEWERS DISCRETION IS ADVICED: This novel is just a giant self-insert</strong></p>

<p>Leon sits at the couch in front of the window of the living room. The day has came to the end, so only few <strong>sunbeams</strong> slide into apartment, <strong>highligting</strong> a teapot with a second <strong>infusion</strong> of chineese tea.</p>

<p>*Bottoms up*. He fills an empty cup gently and starts drinking tea looking trhough the window.</p>

<p>Leon’s apartment are at the very end of the street. The window in the living room is aligned at the center, perpendicular to street. It was amusing for Leon to stare at the dot at which the street perspective converged.</p>

<p>“At some point it feels like <strong>you</strong> are the one who’s being observed…”</p>

<p>Last sunbeam passes. Crumbled walls on <strong>delipidated</strong> houses outside are less noticable now.</p>

<p>The rain started. Some kids and <strong>adolscents</strong> went out to play with a <strong>puddles</strong>. Now they are running home because rain <strong>revved up</strong> to be unbearable. It was to heavy.</p>

<p>It has been raining for hours.</p>

<p>Someone knocks the door. Leon don’t even blink on it.</p>

<p>Knocks are constant now and getting heavier and heavier with every second. Leon tense up.</p>

<p>Five seconds of silense ends with massive hit sound. Intermittent hits are so intensive, the door hinges start crackling. Someone defiently ramed the door with a leg.</p>

<p>“I’m on my way! Stop!”</p>

<p>Leon opens the door. The woman has been standing in front of the opened door. She has <strong>drenched</strong> to the last thread.</p>

<p>“Finally! What a kooky day! Leon, may I stay here till the rain will end? Please!”</p>

<p>Leon is standing, unable to say anything. He is not able to refuse. He <strong>concedes</strong> and nods his head.</p>

<p>“Come in, please, but you act absolutely terr…”
“Thanks, “ lady goes to the living room. She put her purse on the kitchen table.</p>

<p>“What a <strong>stench</strong> here? Why everything is so dirty? And you hair is so <strong>greasy</strong>! Solitude doesn’t affect you well”.</p>

<p>Leon have lost any sense of answering her ridicules and pricks. He decides to go back on the sofa to proceed doing what he has been doing earlier.</p>

<p>Leon enjoys another cup of tea. Just trying not to pay attention on a guest.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="nonsense" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[VIEWERS DISCRETION IS ADVICED: This novel is just a giant self-insert]]></summary></entry></feed>